Whatever hinders your miracle (out). Give way in the name of Jesus!
Give way in the name of Jesus! Give way in the name of Jesus! Give way in the name of Jesus!
I command that disease out!
I say , that disease, leave my people! I say, you affliction, leave my people!
I say leave my people!(amen).
Vomiting Poisonous substances
You know what Jesus can do; within a second, you can get free.
I say, be free in the name of Jesus!
In your blood be free in the name of Jesus!
There is a woman there that is going through some pain.
Yes, it's normal, it will be alright.
I cover you with the blood of Jesus!
Watch your screen and see the strange thing that person has vomited right now.
Praise the Lord! People of God , Emmanuel!
The problem that brought me here is the heart chest pain. The doctors...
I went to the hospital. The doctors said I have infection. Over four years virus,
Its disturbing me long time.
I can not sleep; I can not even live with people if I am together with people ...
Ok. Do you want to sleep? Sleep!
Woman Falls Asleep After A Command From Prophet T.B.Joshua
All authority belongs to Jesus.
He is Lord, He is Lord ; Amen
He has risen from the dead. He is Lord.
Every knee shall bow - every tongue confess that Jesus Christ is Lord.
Testimony Time
People of God, Emmanuel! (God is with us) -Matthew 1:23
My name is Joy Bongos. I am Nigerian. I come from Kano.
Ah The problem that brought me here in Synagogue Church Of All Nations is the virus,
and my chest, the left hand of my chest. Honestly more than four years, I am coughing, coughing
no sleeping, no solution. I went to many places many doctors; there is not way yet there is no solution.
I even to traditio.. the herbs medicine they give it to me, I take it , there is not yet no solution.
That to the extend that my sisters used to call me church prostitute. Why they call me church prostitute is that
anyway they say here they are healing, I will rush there but no way there was no solution.
I suffer for it. If I am in public I will be coughing , coughing no control.
If I am in the church, I will be coughing, in fact I can not feel.
And when I started cough, I will hold my stomach, I will hold my chest
for me to cough. If I did not hold this area, I can not cough it will be paining me.
So, last Sunday I was here sitting up there on the gallery. So Man of God is touching people down.
I say Oh my God why Man of God will not come up and touch me.
I said so people were just telling me you are funny.
and thirty minute time,I say oh my...oh God let Man of God come up.
I sit down. So but the spirit came with me and told me that I should claim it
So whenever Man of God is healing people, I will be claiming - I am healed.
Whenever he touch someone whether its the same sickness with me , I will say, I am healed.
So it started from the Mass Prayer he started praying for people.
Then he said that any thing that is in your liver, you should vomit it out.
So I was there sitting, I feel dizzy in my body then the vomit had come,
I started vomiting from where I sit. When I vomited there for where I sit,
then the usher came and told me ."Come here and vomit." So that's why I come in public.
When I was vomiting, I couldn't know that I am even vomited blood.
I don't know, all of a sudden I just vomited blood, I don't know what happened.
Vomited ..the vomit...let me tell you in short my dear brothers; when I vomiting
it's like someone was using a broom to sweep my heart.
Everywhere was just sweeping. I was just continue vomiting blood.
When the Man of God asked me to sleep; I didn't know I slept up.
And when I was sleeping, something come in my body like it's going out. It's just moving.
In my body, I started stretching my hand, turned and after I turned, I still cough and I vomited again
and some blood still following after when Man of God asked me to sleep.
Then that very Sunday, I go back home. So when I go back home I look at, because you know.....
they give by...I can not sleep without rubbing garlic in my body.
If I did not rub garlic on my body I feel cold started coughing.
But I bring water because I have water 24 hours. I kept water beside me.
Either I will vomit weather I will cough. I sleep like a baby.
I didn't cough, I didn't rub the garlic I didn't do anything. I just sleep up till day break.
When I wake up I said." The God of T.B.Joshua have done, finally I will never cough again."
Shall we clap for Jesus Christ
It was amazing on Monday. I slept very well, fine. Then on Tuesday afternoon.
Haa , oh my God what happened, you know some people used to say they used to dream at night.
But my own dream came in the afternoon, to show that there is power of God from this church.
When I was sleeping on Tuesday afternoon, I saw the Man of God come to me.
He told me, come. I ask him, who are you? he said look at me very well.
I turn , I look at him, I saw him , I say daddy you are the one!
He come, he say yes. He say come to follow me.
I follow him. He went to the other room. He went to the room and he opened the door
of the room. He told me - what did you see there? I said I saw a chain.
Those chains was just tighting very tight. He started breaking the chains in the name of Jesus.
Shall we put our hands together for Christ Jesus!
Then when he break the chain and he give me the key. He said take this key, this is the room
that tied your destiny. Now he has over. I shout!
I say God , thank you, Jesus thank you. Then he told me just stand.
You will see three men are coming, Two men one woman. You will see what will happen.
When they just came; they saw me. They started run away. I say what brought you here?
They say there is fire on your body. There is fir, there is fire
we can't close to you, no no we can not do it again.
That is how they run away. Then Man of God started, in that very afternoon...
He said - get up ! Vomit it again. Which is I still vomit; not in the dream.
I wake up in physical like this, I vomit it again, face to face I see the vomit.
And that was the final?
That was the finally, finally
Shall we put our hands together for Christ Jesus!
Now I am ok. I give God the Glory. I thank Man of God.
I thank Emmanuel TV Partners because without help of prayer, we can not work.
But I believe that God heals me will heal others in Jesus name.
So madam you can sleep well now.
I can sleep very well. Not shaking
Ever since that very day.
Oh my God, you know over four years, I can not sleep but I slept.
The sleep that I did not sleep four years, I slept enough more than the four years.
My dear sister and brother my mummy and daddy; you should believe in God
Yes some other people will say if Man of God did not touch me,
I will not come to church. Why? It's not like that. When you have faith
in you even though, you can see , right now from the television many people are healed.
So when you have faith, everything is come very possible for you.
You just claim it especially that, you know Man of God was saying that - when
I am praying for some others, you should claim it. Claim like that.
Don't say that it's not my my way or it's not the same of the sickness with me. No.
Give faith in God, that God that is doing it for me; because even me sometimes
every time I will say that God you have healed others one day you are going to heal me.
And I found out today I am healed. So because of that;
as I am healed, every one too is going to be healed in the name of Jesus.
Shall we put our hands together for Christ Jesus.
TT Monica Asefa